{
    "subject": "Serge_Gainsbourg",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "\u00c9quateur__film_",
    "human_readable": "Serge Gainsbourg created the film \u00c9quateur.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9228692054748535,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Serge Gainsbourg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8955768942832947,
            "question": "Who created the film \u00c9quateur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8878480792045593,
            "question": "Is Serge Gainsbourg known for filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.86148601770401,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Serge Gainsbourg."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6819995045661926,
            "question": "Who starred in the film \u00c9quateur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6176538467407227,
            "question": "What themes are explored in the film \u00c9quateur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941421985626221,
            "question": "When was the film \u00c9quateur released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5782175064086914,
            "question": "What genre is the film \u00c9quateur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.530353307723999,
            "question": "What other artistic endeavors is Serge Gainsbourg known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30406856536865234,
            "question": "What type of work is \u00c9quateur?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Serge Gainsbourg created the film \u00c9quateur.",
            "html": "yago_21802_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other artistic endeavors is Serge Gainsbourg known for?",
            "html": "yago_21802_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film \u00c9quateur?",
            "html": "yago_21802_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film \u00c9quateur released?",
            "html": "yago_21802_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21802_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents mention that \u00c9quateur is a 1983 French drama film directed by Serge Gainsbourg, which implies that he created the film. Therefore, the triple \"Serge Gainsbourg created the film \u00c9quateur\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Serge Gainsbourg and his work, including that he directed a film called \"\u00c9quateur\" in 1983. This supports the statement that Serge Gainsbourg created the film \u00c9quateur."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}